Hello everyone, let's start today's live broadcast.
Today, we are very honored to invite our little partner, Svea, to participate in our live broadcast today.
Today, Svea will share with you a new digital color design platform called Pantone Connect.
Next, we will give Svea some time to share with you about the Pantone Connect platform.
Hello everyone, I am Svea from Pantone.
Today, I am very happy to receive the invitation from Cloud to share the color inspiration application with everyone.
In 2020, there was a big event that everyone was very surprised and panicked about.
It is the spread of COVID-19.
This matter has actually had a great impact on our traditional design process.
Companies no longer require employees to go to our company to work as usual.
Everyone can choose a remote office.
In fact, this way of working gives our designers
a lot of trouble.
Because we cannot communicate and communicate with each other face-to-face,
we can only send electronic documents to other people for evaluation and evaluation.
And color is one of the design elements that is most affected by this kind of change.
Because remote office means that members of the team cannot face each other in the same environment
and choose colors and communicate with each other.
And remote office brings different environmental lighting,
different computer equipment,
and so on.
This also greatly increases the difficulty of our color processing process.
Many companies, such as Microsoft, Apple, Facebook, and so on,
have announced that they will let their employees work from home for a long period of time.
And remote office has also become a way of working for most people.
And we believe that such a change in working method is not temporary,
but will become a new norm for most people to work.
Just like this picture shows,
the living room or study at home will become a new office for our designers.
Everyone can work freely outside the office.
This also means that our new office may not be the best place to process color.
Because designers have a big difference between working at home and working in the office.
This includes the difference in lighting conditions,
and the lack of professional design tools corresponding to us.
And some computer displays used by each designer
may also be different.
So the fact that we have to admit that
using color to design has actually become a big challenge.
Next, we can take a look at the color process.
What difficulties will we encounter in the color processing process?
On the left side of the work process,
we can see that brands and designers are focused on
transforming the color of their customers' hearts
into color specifications that can be defined and applied,
and displayed in design documents.
Their goal is to choose the right color,
and apply it consistently in design documents
to shorten the time of product listing,
and reduce the overall cost.
On the right side of the work process,
printers and manufacturers need to pre-produce
and finalize the samples provided to the designers.
Their goal is to produce the color in the design documents
accurately and quickly.
But in most cases,
during the color transfer process,
we usually print out these design works,
but because the printed color is incorrect,
or the color cannot be realized,
it will lead to the product color produced by the manufacturer
and the color desired by the designer cannot be matched.
In this process,
some of the higher costs,
approval processes, and time losses
will be borne by our companies.
Based on the above reasons,
we are very happy to be able to
launch such a product with you,
which is our Pantone Connect.
It is a set of integrated
physical, digital, and Internet color work processes.
This application can help our brand and designer friends
to simplify the color work process,
and can also make it more convenient
and easy to communicate
when dealing with color processes
in long-term work.
No matter where you are,
at home or at a meeting,
you can use our Pantone Connect
for color communication.
We have provided a software
that is more than just a mobile device.
It can be easily used by our designers,
brands,
mobile phones,
computers,
tablets,
and Adobe software.
You can easily use our application.
As long as you use our same registered account to log in,
you can log in to all of our clients' accounts
with the same color solution.
We can see that a good design
starts with accurate screen color.
Why do we need to adjust the screen color?
Everyone knows that different displays
display different colors.
In such a situation,
it is actually difficult for us to judge
which display displays the most accurate color.
Especially in team work,
maybe each person uses a different display,
or the display version is different.
So the color we see through the display
may be a little different.
Another point is that
because the screen color is not accurate,
the color we print may also be biased.
So before we start designing,
we need to adjust the screen color.
We can use such a
measurement software of iWall Studio
to establish a display
between the display and the printer.
We can use iWall Studio
to quickly measure multiple devices,
including our display,
printer,
scanner,
and projector screen color.
In addition, our Pantone Connect
will soon be combined with
our iWall Studio measurement products.
It can give you a one-stop color adjustment
and configuration solution.
Also, a good workflow
requires some color management tools
that can be implemented at the same time
to help us.
For example,
in terms of inspiration and selection,
we can use a color comparison card
like the one on the screen
to capture some of the colors
we like to see in our lives.
Next, we can use our Pantone Connect
to check the accuracy of the color.
It is a Pantone color number.
Finally, we can use Adobe software
to design our work
and provide our designers
with an inspiration
and creative design solution
for a complete color solution.
Our Pantone Connect
is now open to all of our
designer friends for free.
Through such a software,
we can extract the colors we like
from some photos in our lives.
We can also share these colors
with our friends,
colleagues,
and colleagues
on social media.
We can also share some of our favorite colors
with the world.
In addition to taking inspiration
from photos,
we can also provide
popular colors for the 2021
London Fashion Week
and New York Fashion Week
for our designers.
We can also give our designers
as a reference for color inspiration.
Through popular colors,
we can also predict
some color trends
that will be popular in the future.
Then our brand and designers
can also design and produce their works
faster,
so that the product can be seen more widely.
When we get inspiration,
we need to convert these inspiration colors
into a color that can be realized.
Then we will need to use
the search function.
Panon Connect can provide
tens of thousands of Panon colors.
From flat printing to package design,
from the most used
brick color,
to the most used
TPG,
TCX colors in the interior of clothes,
we can quickly find them
in this software.
We can also choose
some colors we want
through color selection.
At the same time,
we can meet
different design needs
and provide some
mutual conversion between colors.
For example,
from RGB value to CMYK value,
or to LAB value,
and some conversion between
Panon colors and Panon colors,
we can easily complete
them through this software.
After confirming the color
we want,
we can add them
to the color palette
and save them
to our color palette
for reference
or for sharing with
our design team,
colleagues,
and partners.
In our color palette,
we can add a account
to share with others.
After the other party
log in to Panon Connect,
they can click
our color palette
in their account
to easily find
some colors to share.
Next,
we can use a short video
to find out
what kind of help
Panon Connect can provide.
As you can see
from the video,
our life is actually
surrounded by different colors.
We can use
Panon Connect
to pick up
the colors we like
in our daily life
or in our photos,
or we can use
our color palette
to measure
and capture
some of the colors
we encounter
in our daily life.
We can convert
some of our colors
into Panon colors
that can be realized.
After finding the colors
we want,
no matter where you are,
whether at home
or on the road,
you can use
Panon Connect
to share with
our team
and partners
in real-time.
After determining
the color,
we can use
the color card,
the food color card,
to produce
and collect colors
to ensure that
the final color
and the desired color
of our product
can be used.
Next,
I will show you
what our app looks like.
You can also
scan the QR code
on our website
to download it,
but you need to
use our browser
to open it.
If our
Apple mobile phone user
can use
the App Store,
you can search
for Panon Connect.
After downloading
our software,
first,
we can click
the account
in the upper right corner
to register.
You can use
this
to register
with our
mailbox
or other
third-party
software.
First,
we can see
a panel like this.
In this panel,
we can see
the colors
of all our
Panon products,
including
the color cards
that we use
more often
for our
surface printing
or
our
color
bars
and CMYK values.
We can also
see
the colors of
the most used
TCX,
TPG
and other colors
for our
clothing,
furniture,
and interior.
Click on
this color
and we can
quickly find
the colors
we want.
Click on
this color
and we can
see
its RGB value,
HEX value
and LAB value.
If you think
this color
is too small,
you can check
the product
display.
In addition,
we can also
find
some
matching colors
based on
this color,
such as
some
mirror colors,
color
After saving, we can find them in the color version function.
We can also share the saved color version with our team members.
If we fill in their Rich sorcerags
account, we can easily share it with them.
We can save and save clue cards unit that is shared with us again.
or save clue cards equal to the number of pages shared by the three teams.
So we can save them.
We can also do some color analysis based on such a color palette.
For example, we will provide some color charts, color distribution, brightness chart, and so on.
The second is our search function.
Next to the account, we can find the color we want by searching for such a color number.
For example, 120000.
Then we can find the corresponding color from our PanTong color library.
It may have TCX and TPG.
The second is our extract function.
We can upload such a picture from the photo.
By moving this little light circle,
we can choose some colors we want to extract.
Then we can add this to our color palette to save and share.
Next is a measurement function.
This measurement function is to use our color contrast.
To measure the color contrast.
First, we can see that there is such a color comparison card, we need to scan the QR code on the back of this color comparison card first to identify it.
Then put the color block we want to measure in the color box, and then match the color box and the color card on the mobile phone.
Then our TanTone Connect can automatically measure the colors we want for everyone.
Of course, we can choose the color we want to measure.
Then we can choose the color we want to measure.
The color will have a different material.
For example, the material is cotton, so we can choose TCX.
Here we can see what we have chosen, some of the color overcome colors measured.
Can be used as some reference.
In addition, we can also find some ways to change the color in some of our more features.
For example, some of the RGB values ​​and RGB values ​​can be converted by inputting their LAB values ​​and RGB values ​​to perform corresponding transformations.
The second one is some of our inspiration colors, which is that we can provide some mirror colors and complementary colors that are one color color, etc.
The third one is our popular color version.
We will provide some fashionable colors in the fashion week of Tops.
So that everyone can see it in advance.
To predict what colors will be popular in the future.
And add them to our color palette or save them.
Of course, we can also find some of its colors and images by inputting one Pantone color.
For example, we can see an 1-2-000 color now.
So we can see.
We can see here that.
Their color are similar.
How do they color each other?
Tell you about.
Does it feel different?
How do they color?
Let's start to look at them.
Okay.
So the color patterns are here.
So here we have our green.
The pink.
It looks very cute.
such as color, tone, saturation, and brightness.
Many friends have asked
whether we only have a mobile app.
In fact, in our web page,
we can also find our
Pantone Connect software
for mobile operation.
In addition to the mobile app,
there are also some differences
between our web page
and Adobe software.
You can experience it first.
Next, we will leave the time
to the friends of Cloud.
Then we will share with you
some of the features of Pantone and Cloud.
In addition to the mobile app,
there are also some differences
between our web page and Adobe software.
You can experience it first.
Next, we will leave the time
to the friends of Cloud.
Then we will leave the time
Thank you,
our friends of Pantone.
Sylvia gave us an explanation
about the use of Pantone Connect.
Today,
we will show you
how to design a clothing
in Cloud
using the colors of our Pantone Connect website.
how to design a clothing in Cloud
In this way,
I will show you
how to design a clothing
in Cloud
from the perspective of a designer.
Then, we will use
the platform I just introduced
to make the color combination
and decoration.
Let's see how the designer
can use these two platforms in Cloud.
Then, let's see how
the designer can contact our team members.
Now, let's have a look at the design
of the accessories categoric.
We can see in this article,
that my 하고 will choose
this concept,
Next, we are going to separate the waistline from the waistline, and then add a belt design at the waist end, and we can use the internal line tool to make it.
Okay, I'm going to shorten the proportion of this belt, and then we can enter a width of 60%.
Okay, so we're going to go from a loose belt like this to a belt with a belt like this.
A design
Then we can modify the waist of the plate.
I'm going to shrink the side waist on both sides by three centimeters.
This will make our waist look deeper.
Okay, I'm going to extend his skirt.
Okay, I'm going to extend him 35-centimeter.
Well, we can see that it's like this.
It's going from a t-shirt like this.
It's going from a t-shirt like this to a long skirt like this.
Let's move on to some designs.
Well, I'm going to multiply our оно
As you can see, we can see that we have changed the neckline from a tight one to a loose one.
Next, I will make some simple adjustments to this plate, such as turning the side seam into some straight lines.
Let's adjust the shape of our sleeve. I want to turn it into a long sleeve like this, so we can extend our sleeve length directly.
We can enter a specific length that we need to extend, for example, I will extend it by 40 cm.
Then when you are making collage, you will encounter such a problem, that is, after I made a lot of adjustments to this plate, the plate penetrates into the human body.
Then we can rearrange the plate again. Then we will simulate it again, and it will be very stable, and you can see that it is very convenient.
Next, I would like to make this sleeve into such a speaker sleeve design.
Let's take a look.
Let's see how to adjust it.
I will continue to use the extension plate to adjust it.
Okay, let's simulate it.
Such a sleeve will be from a straight one to a loose one like this.
Next, I want to add such a drawstring to the sleeve so that it can be drawn.
Then I can create such an internal line for it.
So what's this?
It's a Auftrag line.
Just like this, we can create a drawstring effect from it.
What is this?
This is the inner line of the sleeve.
Then we can draw it like this.
What is the inner line of the sleeve?
It's a curve like this.
I want to make a stamen and an inner line.
So we can draw a line.
I can draw a line like this.
After we simulate it, we can see that it has the effect of drawing a wrinkle here.
We can adjust the proportion of this leather to adjust the firmness of our sleeve.
Here, I want to make an inner line.
Then I will close it.
Okay, now I move around a little bit.
We can also add a specific length of the thread to achieve accuracy.
You can see that our sleeve has a wrinkled design like this.
Next, I would like to add a division to the front of the sleeve.
We can open the basic line.
After opening, we can use a 3D pen tool to create a line in the 3D window.
After drawing the line with a 3D pen, we can use the 3D pen tool to turn it into an internal shape to facilitate our next creation.
You can see that this line is not very smooth.
Let's draw it.
Let's make some slight adjustments to make it smoother.
After the line is finished, we can cut it and sew it.
In this way, we can get a division like this.
Next, we will add a cross-sectional plate.
There is a large cross-sectional plate design in front of the chest.
First, we will make a plate for it.
First, we will apply a layer of glue.
Next, we will make a layer of glue.
Next, we will apply a layer of glue.
Then put the plate on the sleeve.
Okay, then we can see that the version has been recognized.
Then we click on the simulation.
You can see that in front of my chest, I have added a design of a lotus leaf board like this.
Next, I will add a lotus leaf board like this to my group board.
The method is the same as before.
First of all, let's make a board like this.
Then we can turn this lotus leaf board into an arc and continue to use our extension board tool.
After the board is made, we will sew it.
Then we will sew it.
You can see that in this way, I quickly designed a dresser with a puller from a basic model like this.
Then we will do some details on this costume.
For example, I give it a waist belt to increase it.
We can also make a double-layer design on the upper part of the dresser.
We can make a cologne out of it.
We need to simulate it to stabilize it.
After the costume is finished, we can start to make the costume.
We can use a different material fabric to find our fabric.
We can find a silk like this first.
We can simulate it.
You can see that after using the silk fabric, the shape of the 3D window's clothing has changed.
We can select some of the panels and apply another material to it.
For example, we can use this learning method.
You can see that this design is very beautiful.
There is a comment saying that this needs to be lowered by a particle scale.
When we made the style in the early stage, it didn't have to be lowered so low.
Let's adjust the shape of the clothing.
Next, we need to match the color of this clothing.
When matching the color, we can cooperate with the Pantone Connect website that we just introduced.
We can see that I have opened a computer version of its website.
Its interface is the same as our mobile phone.
We can see that we can find a collection window here.
After we click on it, we can enter such a interface.
Then we can open the file that we need to extract the color.
You can also put your inspiration picture in it.
Then click on this folder.
We can select some of the inspiration pictures we prepared before.
For example, we can select a blue-colored picture like this.
Then click on this picture.
After this brief identification, it will help you to identify some colors in this inspiration picture.
You can also adjust the colors in it according to your needs.
For example, I feel that this color is too light or too dark.
Then I can make a choice through the mouse to take the color I want.
You can see that it is very convenient.
After we have absorbed this set of colors, we can create a color palette for this set of colors.
We can enter a plant like the introduction just now.
Then make some instructions, for example, give it a name called electric blue.
Add some labels, then we can click save.
When you are going to absorb this color, you should pay attention to your color library.
You have to choose what suits you.
It is suitable for you.
It is a color palette for different industries.
Now we usually use a color library about home-made products.
Then we can choose this color library.
Everyone should pay attention because the colors of our different industries will have different colors.
After we have created this set of colors, we can directly click download.
Then it can download a S-RGB format.
Let's click on it.
It will download the file very quickly.
Then we can open our file in the folder.
There is a file that we have just downloaded.
Then we drag it to the desktop.
Its file format is A-S-Z.
It is an A-S-E.
Next, we can choose our material.
Then open our color.
After clicking on the color, we can enter a picture of our color selection.
Everyone knows that our cloud has already integrated our Pantone color.
We can add it on the right side and click on the plus sign.
Then I can select the color bag I just downloaded.
Select it and then drag it in.
We click open.
Then we can see that this is the color we just extracted from the inspiration picture.
Then we can match these colors to our clothing.
We can select this blue or other blue to match the colors.
Then we can select this blue or other blue to match the colors.
After we have confirmed the color and the fabric, we can make some adjustments to the clothing to improve our quality.
After we improve the quality, the details of our clothing will be more realistic.
As you can see, in our 3D window,
we can add some details to our clothing.
I want to add some buttons on the waist.
We can use the button tool directly.
It's not a button, it's a pearl.
After adding the button, we can choose the button.
After choosing it, we can adjust the pattern of the buttons.
We can choose a button that is closer to the pearl shape.
We can adjust the width and thickness of the button.
We can also make a change to the material of the button.
We can change it to a silk material like a pearl.
We can also continue to design the clothing.
For example, we can copy the button we use and adjust its size.
We can make a small pearl button on the waist.
We can also make a big pearl button on the waist.
By sharing the pattern inside the button,
we can create and adjust the pattern at will.
We can order the button in each area
for each item inside the pattern.
By adding the buttons on the waist as shown,
we make it easier to pass around.
By adding the each pattern inside the button,
In this way, we have quickly completed a set of such designs, and we have used a very accurate Pantone number.
You can see that this side will show the current Pantone number 18-4231, a number of TCX.
In this way, no matter in the design production life or in the actual production life,
we have these four numbers, so we can accurately convey the design of our color.
We can make a new rendering of this clothing to check its effect.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, when we are rendering here, you may see that there are some lags.
Here we have some works that we showed you in the preview.
The next group of links is the one we just made through this method.
As you can see, it's very convenient.
Then we will display it with the same inspiration picture.
Okay.
As you know, we have released a rendering of the laser fabric after Colour 6.0.
We can see that there is a good rendering picture here.
We can see a very beautiful matte fabric like this.
At the same time, its background is also an inspiration picture like this.
When we design this work, we can also use our Pantone Connect platform to extract our inspiration colors.
Let's take a look at how this beautiful skirt is made.
Okay.
Let's open our Pantone Connect platform.
We still come to the Pantone Connect website.
Then we can upload new images.
Then we click open.
Then we can see that it was extracted through a short time.
We can automatically extract a few of these colors
Then we can make some selections for the same level of color
Okay, then we get this group
After extracting the correct Pantone color number
We still follow the same method
Create a color palette like this
Then we can download this color palette
Okay, if you want to see the rendering data
Wait a moment
I'll show you here
Let's take a look at it
Then we can first
The color palette we just extracted
Copy it out
Okay, add it to the desktop
You can see here
I prepared a laser for him
Then we open the one we just made
This is the one we just made
Just add it
Then we choose our main material here
We adjust the color of his main material
After we open it
Load in the color we just created
And then choose the main tone of this piece of fabric
Then click OK
At the same time
We are going to change our fabric type to the attribute of this laser
We click to select
That you can see the attribute of laser
Only available when it is rendered
Let's choose it.
Then we can go under the laser
To change our color
It's our color change
It's also a laser
You can call it whatever you want
Then we can adjust the color below
We can choose 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 individually
Then we can use it at the same time
We just absorbed some of the colors from this material
Go ahead and match
Okay, you can give it to us in the three windows
So you can't see what our color is like
Then we are going to enter it at this time
Blending window
Let's click on the synchronization
You can see that in our blending window
It's very clear
Just like this one we just had
A piece of fabric with a color change effect
Blended it out
Blends it out
And so we can change the color
We want to get a察 presentation
I'm not going to give it one
SO competed
You can change the color
Excellent
Very well
Thank you very much
Sure
Well
Let's see
This is achievable
So what is currently the result
What we have.
That we just would like today
So all that we do.
This is basically we've just like
This skirt is created by combining the above methods with our Pantone platform to create a skirt that has the effect of changing colors.
In this way, we can greatly extend our understanding of the design to get more matching colors.
Some of you just want to see my rendering preview.
I didn't do any preview here.
I just changed the material type to the option of changing colors.
Next,
I will adjust the color of the skirt to get this skirt.
That's it!
The above is my design for the website of Cloud and Pantone Connect.
As you all know, the color of Pantone 2021 has been released in the last two days.
Next, I will introduce the latest representative color of Pantone to you.
刚刚看到有很多同学在弹幕里留言说分不清潘通和彩通。
其实是这样的,就是我们的英文名是潘通,但是我们官方中文名其实是彩通。
就是市面上有很多人其实有假冒我们的一些品牌。
所以建议大家可以关注我们的右边这样的一个二维码,是我们的官方那个微信公众号。
然后左边这样的一个二维码可以去用扫码下载我们的潘通的Connect一个软件。
然后另外的话,这边也留了我的联系方式,如果大家有什么问题的话可以跟我联系。
或者说关注我们的官方微信号可以跟我们联系。
接下来跟大家分享一下我们的一个。
嗯。
网页版的这样的一个潘通Connect。
其实在大家可以看到在左边的这样一个菜单栏中我们可以看到刚才介绍的像手机端上的一些功能,比如说选择颜色,转换颜色,调色版,核心色,提取颜色等等。
另外的话我们也可以看到我们这个潘通2021年的一个代表年度代表色的一些相关的一些信息。
比如说我们。
颜色的这个色号。
我们的极致灰的它在棉布色卡中的一个色号,以及它对应的最佳匹配的在平面印刷中的一个CU卡的一个色号,以及亮丽黄相应对应的一些颜色的色号都可以很清楚的可以看到。
在往下看的话,我们可以看到有几个颜色。
有几个系列的一些颜色。
我们首先是鸟舍。
鸟舍的话是一组比较活泼欢乐的一些颜色。
就是我们在这里我们提供了对应的这样的一个调色盘。
我们可以通过分析颜色的一些数据,也可以保存下来,添加到我们的调色版的工作区,去和我们的朋友朋友们合作伙伴一起去分享。
。
and the color is also relatively bright and strong.
Next, I will explain it one by one.
You can go to our Pantone Connect page
or the mobile phone page to find our annual representative colors
and some stories of its color series.
The second one is that we actually have such an official website,
which is PantoneCN.com.
You can see some stories behind our annual representative colors
and some ways to download them through our website.
If you have any questions, you can contact us through our official channel.
Thank you, Pantone.
See you next time.
This is a video shared by our partners about the 2021 color of the year.
What about here?
I just saw Pantone's annual representative colors two days ago.
After the release,
we quickly made two designs like this.
We can see that this is a dress match made with our
Liang Lihuang and Ji Zhihui.
This is a high-gloss rendering of it.
You can see that
this is a color match of a bag like this.
We can see some of these designs here.
This is two soldiers of DAYEORAH TEN MR.
This photo was filmed in the typical way,
by a déc deuts in 2015.
This photo wasils you can also capture in the mobile application of our website.
We can see that they are working in these sports sales...
Let's look at the crowd calories to see what kind of result we can get.
Yes, I can see time lags.
This is a話 brackets.
This is a high-dose identity.
Dil탕 was still here.
Great.
All of the statistics we came to know,
we will share again.
Thank you all.
Compare to this video,
Let's go back to the Pantone Connect website.
As you can see, there are a lot of popular colors here.
We can directly click on the download,
and then download it to our software,
and upload it to our cloud to do some design.
After today's live broadcast,
let's quickly do some design and sharing about colors.
Today, our live broadcast is coming to an end.
If you have any questions,
we can talk about it together.
I saw that there were some friends in the chat
saying why there are only three types of your model posture.
I don't know if you have it on the top of the software.
There is a download button here to download the latest material.
We have many types of posture that can be downloaded.
Well, this one,
our QR code,
everyone quickly screenshot and save.
Next,
let's take a look at our year-end birthday party.
At the end of this year,
we will have a year-end birthday party.
Everyone,
after a year of our master straight car learning,
everyone should have some good works.
You can send some of your works to our email.
We will share some of everyone's works with you at the end of the year.
If you have any related questions,
you can also leave a message in our email.
We will answer them for you.
Do you have any new questions?
If there is no problem,
we will end the broadcast.
Our final selected works will have special prizes.
There are prizes.
Okay,
thank you for watching today.
we are going to end here.
See you in two weeks.